Harold H. Burton Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Senate File, 1926-1947 (Box 13-55)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1945 (Box 13-49)
    - General
      - Clemens, Erwin L., 1945
      - Cleveland, Ohio, City Council, 1943-1945
      - Cleveland Aviation Club, Cleveland, Ohio, 1944-1945
      - Cleveland Chamber of Commerce, Cleveland, Ohio, 1944-1945
      - Cleveland Grays, Cleveland, Ohio, 1943-1945
      - Cleveland Plain Dealer, 1941-1945
      - Coffin, Ogden W. L., 1942-1945
      - Cohn, Julius B., 1943-1945
      - Colegrove, Kenneth, 1943-1945
      - Commission on Ministerial Training, Methodist Church, Nashville, Tenn., 1944-1945
      - Conference of the Minority, 1944-1945 See also Container 53, Conference of Republican Senators
      - Congratulatory letters on election to the Senate, 1940, (3 folders)
      - Congressional Record
        - Forms, 1944
        - Letters, 1944-1945 (Box 30)
      - Constituent reports See also Container 53, Constituent Reports, Mailing Lists
        - 1941, Aug. 11, First Semiannual Report
        - 1942
          - Feb.19, Second Semiannual Report
          - Apr. 17, Speech to Maine Republican Convention
          - July 15, Third Semiannual Report
          - Sept. 8, Alaska and West Coast Trip
        - 1943
          - Jan. 15, Fourth Semiannual Report, (4 folders)
          - Mar. 27, Resolution to Win the Peace
          - July 15, Fifth Semiannual Report, (2 folders)
          - Oct. 6, Recess Report
        - 1944 (Box 31)
          - Jan. 24, Sixth Semiannual Report, (2 folders)
          - Feb., America's Road to Lasting Peace, (3 folders)
          - July 21, Seventh Semiannual Report
        - 1945
          - Feb. 6, Eighth Semiannual Report
          - Mar., North Africa and Middle East Trip
            - Miscellany, 1945
            - Soldiers' families, 1944-1945, (4 folders)
          - July 26, Ninth Semiannual Report
          - Nov. 1, Final Report
      - Cooperative Committee, Washington, D.C., 1941-1945
      - Cornell, Fred A.
        - 1941-1942
        - 1943-1945, (3 folders) (Box 32)
      - Coudenhove-Kalergi, Richard N., Count, 1941-1945
      - Curtis Publishing Co., 1942-1945
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1941-1945, undated, (8 folders)
      - Danner, F. W., 1945
      - Davidson, William H., 1940-1945
      - Davies, A. Powell, 1944-1945
      - Dugan, Howard F., 1942-1945 (Box 33)
      - “D” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, undated, (5 folders)
      - Elliott, Randall T., 1942-1945
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, (2 folders)
      - Fenn College, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Ferro-Enamel Corp., Cleveland, Ohio, 1945
      - Field, Ben F., 1941-1945
      - Fletcher General Hospital, Cambridge, Ohio, 1944-1945
      - Flor, Grace A., 1941-1944
      - Flynn, John R., 1944
      - Fuerst, John J., 1942-1945
      - “Fa-Fo” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, (3 folders)
      - “Fr-Fu” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, (2 folders) (Box 34)
      - General Tire and Rubber Co., Akron, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Gilhooly, Edward W., 1944-1945
      - Gillespie, Margaret E., 1941-1945
      - Glauser, Glenn, 1941-1945
      - Greater Cleveland Safety Council, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Griswold, Merrill, 1945
      - Gros, John, 1945
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, (5 folders)
      - Hadden, John A., 1942-1945
      - Hagerman, Earl E., 1941-1945, (3 folders)
      - Hale and Hale Co., Cleveland, Ohio, 1943-1945
      - Hamilton Foundry and Machine Co., Hamilton, Ohio, 1944-1945
      - Hanna, Harry A., 1944-1945
      - Hansen, Harry N., 1944-1945 (Box 35)
      - Hart, Earl E., 1941-1945, (7 folders)
      - Hart, Richard E., 1942-1945
      - Haydon, Stuart, 1944-1945
      - Headley, Sanford A., 1942-1945
      - Hensel, Leroy C., 1945
      - Hotel Cleveland, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Hubbell, Charles H., 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - Hummell, Edward J., 1941-1945
      - Hunt, Graham P., 1945
      - Huntington, Hugh, 1941-1945
      - Hyatt, Hudson, 1944-1945 (Box 36)
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1942-1945, (7 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1944-1945
        - A-N, (8 folders)
        - O-Z, (4 folders) (Box 37)
      - Invitations declined, A-Y, 1944-1945, (11 folders)
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1943-1945 (Box 38)
      - Jamison, Robert H., 1941-1945, (5 folders)
      - Jeffrey, Harry P., 1942-1945
      - Jones, Nathaniel M., 1945
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1943-1945, (2 folders)
      - Kaiser, Walter J., 1944-1945
      - Keenan, Joseph B., 1942-1945
      - Keller, O. E. M., 1942-1945, (2 folders)
      - King, Lawrence G., 1944-1945
      - Kinsman Jewish Center, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Klein, Joseph J., 1943-1945
      - “Ka-Kl” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, (2 folders)
      - “Kn-Ky” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, (2 folders) (Box 39)
      - Lake Carriers' Association, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Laubscher, Edwin E., 1943-1945
      - Levin, Samuel A., 1941-1945
      - Lincoln, James F., 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - Lindsay, J. W., 1945
      - Logan, Charles R., 1944
      - Lupton, Dilworth, 1941-1945, undated
      - Lyons, Frank C., 1944-1945
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1942-1945, (4 folders)
      - MacFadden Publications, Inc., 1943-1945
      - Mahaffie, Charles D., 1944-1945
      - McDonnell, Ralph P. S., 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - McGregor, J. Harry, 1941-1945
      - McQuaid, G. O., 1944-1945
      - Military Order of the Purple Heart, General Moses Cleveland Chapter, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Miller, Roy M., 1941-1945
      - Moore, John S., 1943-1945 (Box 40)
      - Morgan, Walter E.,1943-1945
      - Murray, James E., 1942-1945
      - Myron, Louis W., 1945
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1941-1945, undated, (8 folders)
      - NAACP, 1941-1945
      - National Association of Manufacturers, 1941-1945
      - National Committee for Christian Leadership, Washington, D.C., 1945
      - National Council of American War Dads, Kansas City, Mo., 1943-1945
      - National Memorial Stadium Commission for the District of Columbia, 1945
      - New Zionist Organization of America, New York, N.Y., 1945
      - “Na” miscellaneous, 1945
      - “Ne-No” miscellaneous, 1943-1945, (2 folders) (Box 41)
      - Oberlin College, Oberlin, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Ohio Development and Publicity Commission, Columbus, Ohio, 1941-1945
      - Ohio Republican News, 1942-1945
      - Ohio Society of New York, 1942-1945
      - Ohio Society of Washington, D.C., 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - Ohio State University, Columbus, Ohio, 1943-1945
      - Oldham, Annie J., 1944-1945
      - O'Neill, Daniel H., 1945
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1943-1945, (2 folders)
      - Pathfinder (newsweekly), 1943-1945
      - Patrice, Mary, Sister, 1942-1945
      - Patterson, Grove, 1942-1945
      - Pemberton, Lester J., 1943-1945
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1943-1945, (2 folders)
      - Protected Home Circle, Sharon, Pa., 1945
      - “Pa-Pi” miscellaneous, 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - “Pl-Py” miscellaneous, 1943-1945, undated, (2 folders) (Box 42)
      - “Quiz Kids” (radio program), 1945
      - “Q” miscellaneous, 1944-1945
      - Rand, Stuart C., 1945
      - Ray, John F., 1944-1945
      - Redhead, J. H., 1943-1945
      - Republican (magazine), 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - Republican Minority Conference See Container 29, Conference of the Minority
      - Republican National Committee, 1941-1945, (3 folders)
      - Republican State Central and Executive Committee, Columbus, Ohio, 1944-1945
      - Research assistant, 1942-1945, (2 folders)
      - Research Institute of America, Washington, D.C., 1942-1945
      - Richberg, Donald R., 1945
      - Ritzer, Alice, 1941-1945, (3 folders)
      - Roesch, Jack S., 1943-1945 (Box 43)
      - Rollman, Justin A., 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - Rose, William G., 1944-1945
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, undated, (6 folders)
      - Sawtelle, Sherman, 1945
      - Schweid, Edward J., 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - Sepessey, Edward L., 1942-1945
      - Serb, George J., 1944-1945
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1943-1945
      - Smith, Merle P., 1945
      - Smith, Orville, 1945
      - Souder, C. F., 1943-1945
      - Speer, Paul B., 1945 (Box 44)
      - Swetland, Frederic W., 1943-1945
      - Sykora, Loda C., 1941-1945
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1941-1945, (10 folders)
      - Tarbell, Jane G., 1941-1945
      - Taylor, Edward R., 1944-1945
      - Thomas, Evan W., 1944
      - Treaty of Greene Ville Sesquicentennial Commission, Greenville, Ohio, 1935, 1944-1945
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1941-1945, undated, (3 folders) (Box 45)
      - Uhrig, Ann I., 1941-1945
      - United States News, 1941-1945
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Van Buren, Don C., 1943-1945
      - Voorhees, Russell R., 1945
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, undated
      - Wade, Bryon, 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - Wallace, Henry A., 1941-1945
      - Warner, Milo J., 1941-1945, (3 folders)
      - Waterfield, Maynard H., 1942-1944
      - Webb, David K., 1944-1945
      - Weber, Henry, 1945
      - Welday, Harold W.
        - 1943
        - 1944-1945, (2 folders) (Box 46)
      - WGAR Broadcasting Co., Cleveland, Ohio, 1942-1945, (2 folders)
      - Who's Who in America, 1941-1945
      - Wickard, Claude, 1945
      - Wilson, Fred H., 1943-1945
      - “Wings Over Jordan” (radio program), 1941-1945, (2 folders)
      - Wood, Mrs. Edward M., 1942-1945
      - Wood, Gerrit V., 1942-1943
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1941-1945, (7 folders)
      - YMCA of Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1944, (2 folders)
      - Young, Dwight, 1943-1945 (Box 47)
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1945
    - Legislative
      - Aid to Europe, 1945
      - Air transportion, 1945, (3 folders)
      - Alcoholic beverages, 1945
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Bills
        - Printed copies, 1945
        - Requests for copies, 1945, (2 folders)
        - Sponsored by Burton, 1943-1944
      - Bonneville Project, amendments, 1945
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Capitol Page School, Washington, D.C., 1945, undated
      - “C-D” miscellaneous, 1945, (2 folders)
      - Education, 1945
      - Educational broadcasting, 1945
      - Excess profits tax, 1945
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Fair Employment Practices Commission, 1945
      - Form letters, 1945 (Box 48)
      - “F-G” miscellaneous, 1945, (2 folders)
      - Hospitals, 1945, (2 folders)
      - “H-K” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, (2 folders)
      - Lausche, Frank J., 1945
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Missouri Valley Authority, 1945
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, undated
      - National defense housing, 1940-1945
      - “N-O” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Publications received, acknowledgments, 1945
      - “P-R” miscellaneous, 1944-1945, (2 folders)
      - Selective Service Act, 1945
      - Shore and beach erosion, 1945
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Tax adjustment, 1945
      - Territorial Papers of the United States, publication, 1945
      - Thank-you letters, 1945, (3 folders)
      - Transporting troops, 1945 (Box 49)
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Urban redevelopment, District of Columbia, 1945
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1945
      - Veterans of World War I, 1945
      - “V-Z” miscellaneous, 1945, (2 folders)
  - Committees, 1927-1947 (Box 49-52)
    Reports, memoranda, correspondence, maps, and printed matter.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of committee or topic and chronologically or alphabetically therein.
    - Committee on Agriculture and Forestry, 1945 (Box 49)
    - Committee on Appropriations, 1943-1946, (2 folders)
    - Committee on Claims, 1941-1942
    - Committee on Commerce (Box 50)
      - Columbia Power Administration, proposed, 1937, 1942, undated
      - Miscellany, 1941-1945
      - Missouri Valley Authority, proposed, 1945, undated
    - Committee on Education and Labor
      - Fair employment practices, 1944-1945, undated
      - Hospital construction, 1944-1945, undated
    - Committee on Foreign Relations, Senate Resolution 114 re United Nations, 1943, undated
    - Committee on Immigration, 1941-1942, undated
    - Committee on Rules, Capitol Page School, Washington, D.C., 1942-1945
    - Committee on the District of Columbia
      - Bicycle registration, 1943-1944
      - Miscellany, 1943, undated
      - Police and firefighters' salaries, 1942-1943, undated
      - Restaurant sanitary code, 1942-1943
      - Teachers' salaries, 1943
      - Urban redevelopment, 1945, undated, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Mead Committee See same container, Special Committee Investigating the National Defense Program
    - Special Committee Investigating the National Defense Program
      - Alaska and West Coast trip
        - Correspondence and reports, 1942, undated, (3 folders)
        - Maps, 1927-1947, undated, See also Oversize, (2 folders)
      - Food production, 1942-1943
      - Middle East trip, 1938-1945, undated See also Oversize, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 52)
      - Miscellany, 1941-1945, undated, (2 folders)
      - Pan-American Highway, 1945, undated
    - Special Committee to Investigate Gasoline and Fuel Oil Shortages, 1942-1943, undated See also Oversize, (3 folders)
  - Miscellany, 1926-1946 (Box 53-55)
    Campaign material, election statistics, reports, minutes, legal files, voting record, and petitions.
    Arranged alphabetically by topic, type of material, or name of organization and chronologically therein.
    - Campaign material, 1940 See also Oversize (Box 53)
    - Conference of Republican Senators, reports and minutes, 1944-1945, undated See also Container 29, Conference of the Minority, (2 folders)
    - Congressional directory, 1943
    - Constituent reports, mailing lists, undated See also Container 30, Constituent Reports, (3 folders)
    - Election statistics, Ohio, 1940
    - Federal Labor Relations Bill, undated
    - Financial records, 1941-1946, undated
    - Form letters, 1942-1943, undated
    - Mowrer, Edgar Ansel, newspaper columns, 1944-1945, (5 folders) (Box 54)
    - Notes and background material, 1939-1945, undated
    - Petitions, undated
    - Research Institute of America, New York, N.Y.
      - Printed matter, 1943-1945
      - Reports, 1944-1945, (3 folders)
    - Seaboard Terminals Corp., Baltimore, Md., legal file, 1926-1942, (10 folders) (Box 55)
    - Senatorial courtesy, 1942
    - Voting record, 1945
- Supreme Court File, 1792-1965 (Box 56-325)
  - Correspondence, 1936-1965 (Box 56-125)
    Grouped chronologically by the Court's annual October Term with a final group pertaining to Burton's retired status on the Court. Arranged thereunder alphabetically by name of person or organization or by topic and alphabetically or chronologically therein.
    - October term 1945 (Box 56)
      - Al Koran Temple, Cleveland, Ohio, 1946
      - American Red Cross, 1944-1946
      - American Unitarian Association, 1945-1946
      - Arnold, Stanley N., 1945-1946
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (3 folders)
      - Biggs, John, 1945-1946
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1945-1946
      - Buchanan, John G., 1946
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (6 folders)
      - Cleveland Sesquicentennial Commission, Cleveland, Ohio, 1945-1946 (Box 57)
      - Congratulatory letters, 1945-1946
        - A-E, (12 folders)
        - F-Ma, (15 folders) (Box 58)
        - Mc-V, (16 folders) (Box 59)
        - W-Z, (4 folders) (Box 60)
      - Coudenhove-Kalergi, Richard N., Count, 1946
      - “C-D” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (11 folders)
      - Employment applications, office staff, 1945 (Box 61)
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (2 folders)
      - Fletcher General Hospital, Cambridge, Ohio, 1945-1946
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (4 folders)
      - Gridiron Club, Washington, D.C., 1946
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (4 folders)
      - Hart, Earl E., 1945-1946, (2 folders)
      - Hughes, Marcia H., 1946
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (5 folders) (Box 62)
      - Ihlder, John, 1945-1946
      - “I-J” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (3 folders)
      - Kapp, Nele, 1945-1946
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (3 folders)
      - Lang, Bert W., 1945
      - Law clerks, applications, 1945-1946
      - Lowe, Allen James, 1945-1946
      - “L-M” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (8 folders) (Box 63)
      - Ninety-First Division Association, 1946
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (3 folders)
      - O'Toole, John T., 1946
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (2 folders)
      - Palmer, Arthur L., 1945-1946
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1945-1946
      - “P-Q” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (4 folders) (Box 64)
      - Reder, Jacob and Erna, 1936-1945, undated See also Oversize, (2 folders)
      - Reeder, Spencer W., 1945-1946
      - River and Harbor Improvement Association, Cleveland, Ohio, 1945-1946
      - Ruggles, Kent, 1946
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (3 folders)
      - Salter, Katherine H., 1945-1946, (2 folders)
      - Salvation Army, 1945-1946
      - Sawtelle, Sherman C., Jr., 1945-1946
      - Scholefield, Harry B., 1946
      - Sessions, Gilpin S.
        - 1945
        - 1946, (11 folders) (Box 65)
      - Smith, Martha, 1945
      - “Sa-Sn” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (4 folders)
      - “So-Sz” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (2 folders) (Box 66)
      - Tend, Charles W., 1945-1946
      - Thirty-Seventh A.E.F. Veterans Association, Cleveland, Ohio, 1945
      - Truman, Harry S., 1945-1946
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (3 folders)
      - Ulmer, J. M., 1945-1946
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1945-1946
      - Vacation, 1946
      - Valentine, Edward A., 1945-1946
      - Von Cseh, Louis, 1945
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1945-1946
      - West Publishing Co., 1945-1946
      - Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio, 1946
      - “Wa-Wi” miscellaneous, 1945-1946, (5 folders)
      - “Wo-Wy” miscellaneous, 1945-1946 (Box 67)
      - YMCA, 1945-1946
      - “Y” miscellaneous, 1945-1946
      - Zapf, Larry C., 1945-1946
      - “Z” miscellaneous, 1945-1946
    - October term 1946
      - Adams, Elston, 1946-1947
      - Adlesic, Juro and Vera, 1945-1947
      - American Bar Association
        - Miscellany, 1947, (2 folders)
        - Simmons, Robert G., 1946-1947
      - American Law Institute, 1947
      - American Legion, 1946-1947
      - American Red Cross, 1946-1947
      - American Unitarian Association, 1946-1947
      - Anderson v. Mt. Clemens Pottery Co., 1946-1947
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders)
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1946-1947
      - “Ba-Be” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (2 folders)
      - “Bi-By” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders) (Box 68)
      - Community Chest Federation, Washington, D.C., 1946-1947
      - Cowdery, M. A., 1946-1947
      - Crank letters, 1945-1947, undated
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (4 folders)
      - Duckett, Gilbert and Zelma, 1946-1947
      - “D” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders)
      - Everson v. Board of Education, 1947, (2 folders)
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1946-1947
      - Francis, Willie, regarding, 1947 (Box 69)
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders)
      - Golden, Abram A., 1947
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders)
      - Harrison, Earl G., 1947
      - Hart, Earl E., 1945-1947
      - Hattie M. Strong Foundation, 1946
      - Haydon, Stuart, 1946-1947
      - Hoover Co., 1947
      - Hot Springs, Ark., students, 1947
      - Hurst, Mary A., 1946
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (4 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1946-1947, undated, (2 folders)
      - Invitations declined, 1946-1947 (Box 70)
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1946-1947
      - Jacobson, Martin D., regarding, 1946
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Atlantic City, N.J., 1946-1947
      - “J-K” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders)
      - Law clerks, applications, 1946-1947
      - Lehmann, William K., 1946
      - Lewis, John L., regarding, 1946-1947
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (2 folders)
      - McCormick, Margaret E., 1947
      - McGaffigan, James H., Jr., 1947
      - McMillian, Eugene L., 1946-1947
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders)
      - Nation Associates, 1947
      - National Conference for the Prevention and Control of Juvenile Delinquency, Washington, D.C., 1946
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1946-1947
      - O'Neill, Daniel H., 1946-1947
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Box 71)
      - Pearson, Drew, regarding, 1947
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1946-1947
      - “P-Q” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders)
      - Rhyne, Charles S., 1946-1947
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (2 folders)
      - Salvation Army, 1946-1947
      - Sawtelle, Sherman C., 1946-1947
      - Scheff, Benson H., 1947
      - Sessions, Gilbert S.
        - Sept. 1946-Feb. 1947, (7 folders)
        - Mar.-Sept. 1947, (5 folders) (Box 72)
      - Shafroth, Morrison, 1947
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (3 folders)
      - Trimble, Jesse, 1947
      - Truman, Harry S. See Container 70, National Conference for the Prevention and Control of Juvenile Delinquency
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1946-1947
      - Unitarian Service Committee, Boston, Mass., 1946-1947
      - United States v. National Lead Co., 1947
      - “U-W” miscellaneous, 1946-1947, (4 folders)
      - Yee-Quil, Cornelia N., 1947 (Box 73)
      - YMCA, 1946-1947
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1946-1947
    - October term 1947
      - Address changes, 1947-1948
      - Atgeld Centenary Committee of Illinois, Chicago, Ill., 1947-1948
      - American Hospital Association, 1947-1948
      - American Law Institute, Philadelphia, Pa., 1948
      - American Legion, 1947-1948
      - American Unitarian Association, 1947-1948
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1947-1948
      - Bahnsen, Armin F., 1946-1948
      - Bertram, Tex., students, 1948
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1947-1948
      - Burton, Selma, 1947-1948
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (3 folders)
      - Cleveland Bar Association, Cleveland, Ohio, 1948
      - Cleveland Chamber of Commerce, Cleveland, Ohio, 1947-1948
      - Community Chest Federation, Washington, D.C., 1947-1948
      - Crank letters, 1948, undated
      - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, board of elections, 1946-1948
      - “Ca-Cl” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (2 folders)
      - “Co-Cz” miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 74)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1947-1948
      - “D-E” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (2 folders)
      - Flor, Grace A., 1948
      - Freemasons, 1948
      - “F-G” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (2 folders)
      - Hopper, Pariska, 1948
      - Hubbell, Charles H., 1947-1948
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (2 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1947-1948
      - Invitations declined, 1947
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1947-1948
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Atlantic City, N.J., 1947-1948
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1947-1948
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1947-1948
      - Law clerks, applications, 1948
      - Lodge, Harry L., 1948
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (2 folders) (Box 75)
      - McCollum v. Board of Education, 1948-1949, (2 folders)
      - McDonnell, Ralph P. S., 1947-1948
      - Meharry Medical College, Nashville, Tenn., 1948
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (3 folders)
      - National Association of Women Lawyers, speech, 1948
      - Newton High School, Newtonville, Mass., 1947-1948
      - Ninety-First Division Association, 1947-1948
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1947-1948
      - Office of the Clerk, 1947-1948
      - Office of the Reporter, 1947-1948
      - Ohio State Safety Council, Cleveland, Ohio, 1948
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1947-1948
      - Pearson, Drew, re article by, 1948
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1947-1948
      - Philately, 1946-1948
      - Publications ordered, 1947-1948
      - Putnam, John B., 1947-1948
      - “Pa-Pi” miscellaneous, 1947-1948